Guide to the Joseph Barnes Papers
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series III: Uncataloged Papers
  - Gruber Ruth (Box 26)
  - Guggenheim Foundation (Box 26)
  - H (Box 26)
  - Hailey. Foster (Box 26)
  - Heilbroner, Robert L. (Box 27)
  - Hempstone, Smith (Box 27)
  - Holton, Gerald (Box 27)
  - Hoyt. Edwin P. (Box 27)
  - Instttute of Pacific Relations (Box 27)
  - Israel (Box 27)
  - J (Box 27)
  - Johnstone, Erie. Jr. (Box 27)
  - Joseph, Dov "Barney" (Box 27)
  - Jouhaux, Leon (Box 27)
  - K (Box 27)
  - Kaplan, Justin D. (Box 28)
  - Kayden, Eugene M. (Box 28)
  - Kennan, George. 1845-1924 (Box 28)
  - Kennan, George Frost (Box 28)
  - Kerr. Walter (Box 28)
  - King. Hortense & Wyncle (Box 28)
  - Knox. John (Box 28)
  - Kugelmass, Joseph (Box 28)
  - Kurtz, Howard G. (Box 28)
  - Lamont. Corliss & Margaret (Box 29)
  - Lattimore, Owen & Eleanor (Box 29)
  - The Lauterbach Award (Box 29)
  - Lauterbach. Richard E. (Box 29)
  - Loewenberg. Bert James (Box 29)
  - M (Box 29)
  - McCarthy/McCarran Committees (Box 29)
  - Magazine subscriptions (Box 29)
  - Magnes, Beatrice L. (Box 29)
  - Malraux, Andre (Box 29)
  - Mandelstam. Osip (Box 29)
  - Matthews. Herbert Lionel (Box 29)
  - Miers, Earl Schenck (Box 30)
  - Munger, Edwin S. (Box 30)
  - N (Box 30)
  - National Translation Center (Box 30)
  - The Nation (Box 30)
  - New weekly magazine (Box 30)
  - New York University, 1960-62 (Box 30)
  - Newman, James R (Box 30)
  - Nilin, Pavel (Box 30)
  - Nolte, Richard H. (Box 30)
  - Norden, Heinz (Box 30)
  - Norris, Edgar Hughes (Box 30)
  - O (Box 31)
  - O'Brien, Conor Cruise (Box 31)
  - Oeberg, Torgny (Box 31)
  - Oppenheimer. J. Robert (Box 31)
  - P (Box 32)
  - Parkin, Ralelgh (Box 32)
  - Passport problems, 1957 (Box 32)
  - Pauker, John (Box 32)
  - Paustovsky, Konstantine (Box 32)
  - Pearlman, Moshe (Box 33)
  - Phillips, Harlan B. (Box 33)
  - Phillps John (Box 33)
  - Platonov, Andrei (Box 33)
  - Polk, George (Box 33)
  - Public Affairs Committee. inc. (Box 33)
  - Pulitzer, Joseph. Jr. (Box 33)
  - R (Box 34)
  - Reynaud, Paul (Box 34)
  - Richards, A. Newton (Box 34)
  - Rogger, Hans (Box 34)
  - Roosevelt, Belle (Mrs Kermit) (Box 34)
  - Roper, Elmo (Box 34)
  - Rosten, Leo (Box 34)
  - Russian fiction (Box 34)
  - S (Box 34)
  - Salisbury, Harrison E. (Box 34)
  - Saposnick, Nina (Box 34)
  - Sarah Lawrence College (Box 34)
  - Scientific American (Box 35)
  - Scott, John (Box 35)
  - Seale, Patrick (Box 35)
  - Seldes, Gilbert (Box 35)
  - Shannon, Floyd B./The MARC Corporation (Box 35)
  - Shapiro, Henry & Ludmilla (Box 35)
  - Shea, Albert A. (Box 35)
  - Shirer, William Lawrence (Box 35)
  - Silberman de Villiers, Leo (Box 36)
  - Simmons, Ernest J. (Box 36)
  - Simon, Maron J. (Box 36)
  - Simon and Schuster, inc (Box 36)
  - Simonov, Konstantine (Box 36)
  - Slonim, Marc (Box 36)
  - Snow, Edgar (Box 36)
  - Society and Science (Box 37)
  - Solomon, Edward C. (Box 37)
  - Southern Bell Telephone and Telegraph Company (Box 37)
  - Soviet archaeology (Box 37)
  - Steele, A.T. (Box 37)
  - Stone, Judy (Box 37)
  - Strong, Anna Louise (Box 37)
  - Szilard, Leo (Box 37)
  - T (Box 37)
  - Taylor, Harold (Box 37)
  - Taylor, Telford (Box 37)
  - Translation problems (Box 38)
  - Trefilov, Valentin (Box 38)
  - Turner, Ralph E. (Box 38)
  - Twentleth Centuty Studies (Box 38)
  - Tydings, Joseph D. (Box 38)
  - University presses (Box 38)
  - Van Doren, Irita B. (Box 38)
  - Vorspan, Albert W. (Box 38)
  - Warburg, James P. (Box 38)
  - Ward, Harry F. (Box 38)
  - Weiss, Louis Stix (Box 39)
  - Werner, M.R. (Box 39)
  - Werth, Alexander (Box 39)
  - Western Electric (Box 39)
  - Weidemann, Howard M. (Box 39)
  - Whyte. William H. (Box 39)
  - Willkie, Philip H. (Box 39)
  - Willkie, Wendell L. (Box 39)
  - Winner, Percy (Box 39)
  - Wolfert, Ira (Box 40)
  - Worthy, William (Box 40)
  - Wright, Quincy, Wllliam Evan & Morton Deutsch: Preventing World War III (anthology) (Box 40)
  - Writers Freedom Board (Box 40)
  - Writers Freedom Board: Amici Curiae brief (Box 40)
  - Wyzanski, Charles E., Jr. (Box 40)
  - Y (Box 40)
  - Yadin, Yigael (Box 40)
  - Yugoslav information Center (Box 40)
  - Z (Box 40)
  - Zeisel, Hans (Box 40)